how was it?
どうだった?
today?
今日?
It was fun.
楽しかったよ
it was fun?
楽しかった?
Yeah.
うん
It's been a while.
久しぶりだったね
Hasn't it been a month?
1ヶ月あってないの?
Yeah.
うん
We hadn't met.
会ってなかったもんね
Didn't you have sex during that time?
その間、エッチしなかった?
I haven't.
してない
Haven't you?
してない?
It’s been a while since the team?
チーム久しぶり?
Yeah.
うん
long time no see.
久しぶり
It's cute, more so.
可愛いね、もっと
It's not cute.
可愛くない
So you weren't having sex at all?
じゃあ、全然エッチしてなかったの?
I haven't.
してない
What were you doing during that time?
その間どうしてたの?
picture?
え?
Stab me.
刺してよ
picture?
え?
Do you mean stab me?
刺してっていうこと?
Stab me.
刺してよ
So I was doing it alone.
だから、 1人で してたの
Seriously?
マジ?
Because I was lonely.
寂しかったから
Seriously?
マジで?
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
Wow.
す ーって
It's a really beautiful shirt
めっちゃ綺麗なシャツだ
hey.
ね
in front.
前 に
Did it come out?
出てきた?
I won't leave it alone.
放置しないね
It's so embarrassing.
めちゃめちゃ恥ずかしいよ
Just stay like this.
この ままじゃ
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
恥ずかしいでしょ
close.
近い
It's close.
近いのですね
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
恥ずかしいでしょ
It's not embarrassing, is it?
恥ずかしくないでしょ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
This way.
こっち
This one is good too.
こ っち も いいじゃん
lie?
嘘?
It's not a lie.
嘘じゃない
This way.
こっち
Good.
よいしょ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
It's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいのですけど
Let me open it myself.
自分で開いてもらおう
like this?
こう?
copper?
どう?
Hey.
ねぇ
close.
近い
It's pretty close.
だいぶ近いよ
I can see clearly.
は っきり見える
No way.
やだ
Can I take your hand?
手とれていい?
No.
ダメ
why?
なんで?
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
what?
何?
Hey.
ねぇ
what?
何?
Are you still asleep?
まだ眠るの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
terrible.
やばい
I got in here.
ここ入っちゃった
sorry.
ごめん
Did it take?
かかった?
It took a lot of time.
めっちゃかかった
Clothes?
服?
I got caught, really.
バレちゃったな、本当に
Did it take?
かかった?
It took a lot of time.
めっちゃかかった
sorry.
ごめん
what
なん
So you went?
で 行っちゃったの?
some time ago.
さ っき
Did you go first?
先に行っちゃったの?
It felt so good.
気持ちよすぎた
Are you more at ease?
もっと平気?
what?
何?
Are you more at ease?
もっと平気?
Why don't you?
なんでしないの?
Yeah.
うん
do you want to?
したいの?
Yeah.
うん
Amazing tightening
すごい締
circle.
ま る
amazing.
すごい
Are you tightening it?
締めてる?
Not tightened.
締めてない
It's tough.
きついね
It's really tight though.
すごい締まってるけど
Was it like this?
こんな感じだったっけ?
I don't remember.
覚えてない
Don't you remember?
覚えてない?
How did you touch it yourself?
自分でさ、 どんな感じで触ってたの?
By yourself?
自分で?
Try it.
やってみてよ
Oh, a long time ago.
や だ、昔
Are you having morning sickness?
つわるの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
I'm so excited.
すごいビジョビジョしてる
Hold your finger.
指を持ってさ
Good.
よいしょ
Please stand up.
足立ててごらん
Can you put your feet up?
足立てる?
Try moving.
動いてごらん
how?
どうやって?
Try your hand at it.
手ついてごらん
At the back.
後ろに
Try moving.
動いてごらん
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Is it in?
入ってる?
It's in.
入ってるよ
The front is easier to get into.
前のほうが入りやすい
you?
お前?
Maybe the back can move.
後ろのほうが動けるかも
amazing.
すごい